https://www.steamboatchamber.com/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy
The Steamboat Springs Chamber (SSC) respects the privacy and confidentiality of individuals who visit the SSC website located at www.steamboatchamber.com.
SSC maintains this Privacy Policy to inform you about our policies and procedures regarding the collection, use, security, and disclosure of personally identifiable information and other information received from users of the website. This Privacy Policy may be updated or revised from time to time. We may do so, at any time and without notice, by posting the revised version on this website. We suggest that you review this Privacy Policy periodically for any such changes.
By using the SSC website, you consent to the collection and use of information by SSC. If you do not agree with the terms and conditions stated in this Privacy Policy, please do not access or use the SSC website. This Privacy Policy does not apply to any third-party site that may be accessible through this website.
Collection of Your Personal Information
SSC's mission is to provide you with personalized services and offerings designed to enhance your Steamboat experience. To do so effectively, this website facilitates your sending of personally identifiable information to SSC, such as your name, telephone number, postal address or email address. The provision of any such information by you is completely voluntary. If you do not wish your personally identifiable information to be collected, please do not submit it. Please do not send any information that is sensitive or confidential.
When you visit our site, we may collect information sent to us automatically by your web browser. This information typically includes your Internet Protocol (IP) address, the identity of your internet service provider, the name and version of your operating system, the name and version of your web browser, the "referring" website from which you initially entered this website, the date and time of your visit, and the pages you visit.
The SSC website employs "cookie" technology. Cookies are small pieces of data stored in files on your computer allowing SSC to track your use of the website as you visit and revisit the website. The use of cookies by the SSC website complies with generally accepted programming standards and practices. Please note that you can choose to block the use of cookies through settings in your web browser, but certain features of the SSC website may not work properly without them.
Use of Your Information
We do not sell, share or otherwise disclose the personally identifiable information you provide through this website except as follows: (i) disclosures to third parties who perform services on our behalf, such as those who monitor the website and those who assist in preparing mailings. We reserve the right to use and share any information to investigate illegal conduct or violations of the Terms of Use governing this website, to comply with legal process, to assist law enforcement agencies, or if we believe in good faith it is required by law. SSC routinely collects, compiles, and reports statistics and information reflecting the use of the SSC website and information services in order to enhance membership services, improve marketing and promotional efforts, analyze SSC website usage, improve the website's content and layout, generate aggregate reports on trends, interests and behavior and enhance service offerings.
We take reasonable precautions to provide a level of security appropriate to the sensitivity of the personally identifiable information you provide through this website. While we take reasonable measures to ensure the security of this information, we cannot guarantee the security of the information provided over the internet or stored in our databases. Your transmissions are, therefore, at your own risk.
Changing and Deleting Your Personal Information
You may request that SSC change or delete your personal information from the SSC database by submitting a detailed description of the desired action to the following e-mail address: info@steamboatchamber.com. Please note, after SSC processes a change or deletes your personal information from active SSC systems and databases, it is possible that non-active residual copies of your information may still exist in SSC systems and on archive or backup media.
Electronic Newsletters
You may choose to receive promotional or marketing information from our web site steamboatchamber.com or organization by signing up online. We adhere to a strict opt-in policy and will only contact you if you specifically requested to receive information from our corporation via email, paper form or website registration. Steamboat Central Reservations also may contact web visitors via email or direct mail in regards to summer marketing programs.
Opt out: You may choose not to receive promotional or marketing information from our web site steamboatchamber.com or organization by editing your email profile online. Please note our online subscription database is for email marketing programs only. To opt-out from all communications including direct mail, please email info@steamboatchamber.com.
Governing Law
This Privacy Policy shall be governed under the laws of the State of Colorado without regard to its conflicts of law provisions.
Questions and Concerns
If you have questions or concerns about this Privacy Policy or any of SSC's use of your information, please contact SSC at the following e-mail address: info@steamboatchamber.com.
Special Offers in Steamboat
Get Our Emails
Receive not-to-be-missed events, special vacation offers and the scoop on all the activities and happenings.
Free Visitors Guide
Find trail guides, walking tours, seasonal calendar of events, and more insight on visiting Steamboat Springs.
© 2020 Steamboat Springs Chamber, Inc. All rights reserved.
Cookies are used for measurement, ads and optimization. By continuing to use our site you agree to our privacy policy.
